// Lesson one questions

export const questionSetPollution = [
  /*{
    questionType: "Writing",
    question:
      "What is the variety of organisms in an area, by species, genes, populations, and communities called?",
    answer: "Biodiversity",
  },*/
  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "A question about Pollution",
    answer: "All of the above",
    allChoices: [
      "Ok this works thats hype",
      "A city that recycles, reuses, and reduces",
      "A city that reduces the pollution that they generate",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question:
      "Which of the following is a strategy for building a sustainable future?",
    answer: "Using local materials",
    allChoices: [
      "Importing more resources",
      "Using local materials",
      "Developing more nuclear power stations",
      "Creating more waste",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "What is the official definition for sustainability?",
    answer:
      "Understanding how to meet the needs of the present without compromising the needs of future generations to meet their own needs",
    allChoices: [
      "Understanding how to meet the needs of the present generation",
      "Understanding how to meet the needs of the present without compromising the needs of future generations to meet their own needs",
      "Understanding how to meet the needs of the future generations",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "Writing",
    question: "True or false: Litter is a type of pollution.",
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    questionType: "Writing",
    question: "True or false: Plants and trees release oxygen into the air.",
    answer: "True",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "What is a landfill?",
    answer: "A place where trash is piled up",
    allChoices: [
      "A place where trash is piled up",
      "Place where trash is recycled",
      "Place where trash is reduced",
      "Place where trash is reused",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "What does biodegradable mean?",
    answer: "It can be broken down",
    allChoices: [
      "It can be bought",
      "It can not be broken down",
      "It can be broken down",
      "It can be sold",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "What is NOT a sustainable practice?",
    answer: "All are sustainable practices",
    allChoices: [
      "Recycling",
      "Reducing",
      "Reusing",
      "All are sustainable practices",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "Which of the following is not a pillar of sustainability?",
    answer: "Education",
    allChoices: ["Environment", "Economic", "Education", "Social"],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "MultipleChoice",
    question: "Which of the following will help you save water?",
    answer: "Close taps properly and fix leaking taps, pipes & toilets",
    allChoices: [
      "Close taps properly and fix leaking taps, pipes & toilets",
      "Flush the toilet 3 times",
      "Take long showers",
      "Leave the faucet on while you brush your teeth",
    ],
    instructionText: "Press on or drag the best answer to place",
  },

  {
    questionType: "Matching",
    questionAnswerPairs: [
      {
        answer: "Atmosphere",
        question:
          "Air - the layer of Nitrogen, Oxygen, and other gases that surrounds the Earth",
      },
      {
        answer: "Hydrosphere",
        question: "All the oceans and other bodies of water on Earth",
      },
      {
        answer: "Lithosphere",
        question:
          "The crust and the solid outermost layer of the upper mantle - rocks and soil",
      },
      {
        answer: "Biosphere",
        question: "People, animals, plants",
      },
    ],
    instructionText: "Match the definition with the appropriate term",
  },
];
